[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 11, "question": "It was a consensual mutual relationship sexually speaking, wasn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "was", "a", "consensual", "mutual", "relationship", "sexually", "speaking", ",", "was", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "VBG", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 12, "answer": "Yes, always.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "always", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 73, "question": "But are you just going to take that or do you believe there is a genuine prospect of achieving this?", "question_tokens": ["But", "are", "you", "just", "going", "to", "take", "that", "or", "do", "you", "believe", "there", "is", "a", "genuine", "prospect", "of", "achieving", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 74, "answer": "Look, I've been on a mission.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", ",", "I", "'ve", "been", "on", "a", "mission", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NNS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 169, "question": "Do you think people were surprised by what you were telling them?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "people", "were", "surprised", "by", "what", "you", "were", "telling", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "I think many people don't really realize the difference between handgun injury and assault weapons injury.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "many", "people", "do", "n't", "really", "realize", "the", "difference", "between", "handgun", "injury", "and", "assault", "weapons", "injury", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "VBP", "TO", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "CC", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 211, "question": "Is your belief still that the only answer to America's gun violence is more guns?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "your", "belief", "still", "that", "the", "only", "answer", "to", "America", "'s", "gun", "violence", "is", "more", "guns", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "RBR", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 212, "answer": "Well, I think we all want to try to keep criminals from going and getting guns.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "we", "all", "want", "to", "try", "to", "keep", "criminals", "from", "going", "and", "getting", "guns", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "Do you know?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "Well, obviously they were all killed.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "obviously", "they", "were", "all", "killed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 237, "question": "Do they to you?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "they", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 238, "answer": "Look, Piers, let me just ask you a question.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", ",", "Piers", ",", "let", "me", "just", "ask", "you", "a", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 243, "question": "Do you know?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 244, "answer": "The semiautomatic hunting rifles can fire exactly the same number of bullets per minute as your AR-15.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "semiautomatic", "hunting", "rifles", "can", "fire", "exactly", "the", "same", "number", "of", "bullets", "per", "minute", "as", "your", "AR-15", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 269, "question": "So if you remove hunting from the equation, what are you left with as a purpose for these weapons?", "question_tokens": ["So", "if", "you", "remove", "hunting", "from", "the", "equation", ",", "what", "are", "you", "left", "with", "as", "a", "purpose", "for", "these", "weapons", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 270, "answer": "No, no.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 294, "question": "Mr. Lott do you know how many mass shootings there have been in the last 30 years in America?", "question_tokens": ["Mr.", "Lott", "do", "you", "know", "how", "many", "mass", "shootings", "there", "have", "been", "in", "the", "last", "30", "years", "in", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "EX", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 295, "answer": "I mean, I have written papers on it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "I", "have", "written", "papers", "on", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last 30 years"], "PERSON": ["Mr. Lott"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 306, "question": "Do you know what weapons were used in those mass shootings?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "what", "weapons", "were", "used", "in", "those", "mass", "shootings", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 307, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "NNP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "What I don't understand from all the expertise you bring to this, is - and I don't want to put words in your mouth -- but of all the 35 proposals President Obama has put forward, which ones would you actually agree with in terms of introducing more gun safety in America?", "question_tokens": ["What", "I", "do", "n't", "understand", "from", "all", "the", "expertise", "you", "bring", "to", "this", ",", "is", "-", "and", "I", "do", "n't", "want", "to", "put", "words", "in", "your", "mouth", "--", "but", "of", "all", "the", "35", "proposals", "President", "Obama", "has", "put", "forward", ",", "which", "ones", "would", "you", "actually", "agree", "with", "in", "terms", "of", "introducing", "more", "gun", "safety", "in", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "DT", ",", "VBZ", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ":", "CC", "IN", "DT", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", ",", "WDT", "NNS", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "JJR", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "OK, Before I will get to that question, which I will get to, I want to go and deal with the points you were just raising.", "answer_tokens": ["OK", ",", "Before", "I", "will", "get", "to", "that", "question", ",", "which", "I", "will", "get", "to", ",", "I", "want", "to", "go", "and", "deal", "with", "the", "points", "you", "were", "just", "raising", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 335, "question": "Do you know how many there have been since the gun ban was brought in?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "how", "many", "there", "have", "been", "since", "the", "gun", "ban", "was", "brought", "in", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "JJ", "EX", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 336, "answer": "It depends on how you define them.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "depends", "on", "how", "you", "define", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 341, "question": "Do you know how many there have been in Australia since they brought in the gun ban?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "how", "many", "there", "have", "been", "in", "Australia", "since", "they", "brought", "in", "the", "gun", "ban", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "JJ", "EX", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 342, "answer": "Okay.", "answer_tokens": ["Okay", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Australia"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 352, "question": "Now, how many have there been since 1996?", "question_tokens": ["Now", ",", "how", "many", "have", "there", "been", "since", "1996", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "EX", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 353, "answer": "OK.", "answer_tokens": ["OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1996"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 360, "question": "How many since '96?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "since", "'96", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "-NONE-", "."], "aSentId": 361, "answer": "I already said it a couple of times.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "already", "said", "it", "a", "couple", "of", "times", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["'96"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBD", "CD", "IN", ",", "CC", "EX", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 390, "question": "Do you know?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 391, "answer": "There was one before, and there haven't been any after.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "was", "one", "before", ",", "and", "there", "have", "n't", "been", "any", "after", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Sandy Hook"]}, "docId": "130227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 408, "question": "Why am I on?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "am", "I", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "-- following massacres like Sandy Hook -", "answer_tokens": ["--", "following", "massacres", "like", "Sandy", "Hook", "-"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 410, "question": "Why am I on?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "am", "I", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 411, "answer": "They have seen zero mass shootings in one country.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "have", "seen", "zero", "mass", "shootings", "in", "one", "country", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last 10 years"], "LOCATION": ["Germany"]}, "docId": "130227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 425, "question": "How many in the last ten years have been killed by guns in Germany?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "in", "the", "last", "ten", "years", "have", "been", "killed", "by", "guns", "in", "Germany", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 426, "answer": "Germany had both of their shootings in the last 10 years.", "answer_tokens": ["Germany", "had", "both", "of", "their", "shootings", "in", "the", "last", "10", "years", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Germany"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 429, "question": "Do you know?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 430, "answer": "Again, what you have --", "answer_tokens": ["Again", ",", "what", "you", "have", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 432, "question": "Do you know the answer to the country that you raised as an example of proof of your argument?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "the", "answer", "to", "the", "country", "that", "you", "raised", "as", "an", "example", "of", "proof", "of", "your", "argument", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 433, "answer": "No, no!", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", "!"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJR", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 470, "question": "How many people were murdered in Britain last year with guns?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "people", "were", "murdered", "in", "Britain", "last", "year", "with", "guns", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 471, "answer": "OTT: The point is it was even lower before --", "answer_tokens": ["OTT", ":", "The", "point", "is", "it", "was", "even", "lower", "before", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Britain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJR", "NNS", ",", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", ":"], "qSentId": 479, "question": "How many?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 480, "answer": "It makes more sense to talk about murder rates, to deal with differences in populations --", "answer_tokens": ["It", "makes", "more", "sense", "to", "talk", "about", "murder", "rates", ",", "to", "deal", "with", "differences", "in", "populations", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 494, "question": "Do you believe in universal background checks for all guns in America?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "in", "universal", "background", "checks", "for", "all", "guns", "in", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 495, "answer": "In theory, if you could fix the problems with the current background system, that would be great.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "theory", ",", "if", "you", "could", "fix", "the", "problems", "with", "the", "current", "background", "system", ",", "that", "would", "be", "great", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 504, "question": "But of the 35 proposals for gun safety that the president is trying to bring in, how many of the 35 do you support?", "question_tokens": ["But", "of", "the", "35", "proposals", "for", "gun", "safety", "that", "the", "president", "is", "trying", "to", "bring", "in", ",", "how", "many", "of", "the", "35", "do", "you", "support", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "CD", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 505, "answer": "I don't think I supported any of the ones that he had.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "I", "supported", "any", "of", "the", "ones", "that", "he", "had", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "TO", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 516, "question": "Were they?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 517, "answer": "Well, they are pretty serious if you're the father of a boy who has been blown to pieces.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "they", "are", "pretty", "serious", "if", "you", "'re", "the", "father", "of", "a", "boy", "who", "has", "been", "blown", "to", "pieces", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 551, "question": "Have you ever heard a case quite like this?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "ever", "heard", "a", "case", "quite", "like", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 552, "answer": "Never.", "answer_tokens": ["Never", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 603, "question": "Or am I misreading this?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "am", "I", "misreading", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 604, "answer": "Well, I think the prosecution is mishandling this case completely.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "the", "prosecution", "is", "mishandling", "this", "case", "completely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 611, "question": "Marcia Clark, do you see a point to what is going on in this courtroom?", "question_tokens": ["Marcia", "Clark", ",", "do", "you", "see", "a", "point", "to", "what", "is", "going", "on", "in", "this", "courtroom", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 612, "answer": "I do, actually.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", ",", "actually", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marcia Clark"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 633, "question": "Why not make them focus on the deliberate lies that are central to the facts in this case?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "not", "make", "them", "focus", "on", "the", "deliberate", "lies", "that", "are", "central", "to", "the", "facts", "in", "this", "case", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 634, "answer": "OK.", "answer_tokens": ["OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130227pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 657, "question": "If you take him at face value in those private conversations he was having with fetishists, however ghastly the earlier material I read, is he a criminal?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "take", "him", "at", "face", "value", "in", "those", "private", "conversations", "he", "was", "having", "with", "fetishists", ",", "however", "ghastly", "the", "earlier", "material", "I", "read", ",", "is", "he", "a", "criminal", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "RB", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 658, "answer": "Absolutely not.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]